Satoru.
Show him to the dorm.
Explain the security and
everything else to him, too.
Huh?
You pass.
Welcome to Jujutsu Tech.
Fushiguro!
You look like you're doing well now.
There were plenty of other
empty rooms, weren't there?
But isn't livelier better?
I thought it'd be good for—
Classes and missions are enough.
This was an unwelcome favor.
Wow, it's so organized.
I just said you're unwelcome!
Well, it's all good.
More importantly, we're heading out tomorrow!
We're gonna go pick up the third first-year.
The train bound for Shibuya and
Shinagawa is now arriving on track 1.
For your safety, please
stand behind the yellow line.
Saori-chan.
I'm here.
I'm in Tokyo!
How are there only three first-years?
Isn't that too few?
Well, have you ever met anyone
who can see curses before?
Nope.
That just proves how small
a minority jujutsu sorcerers are.
Also, didn't you say I was the third?
Their entry was decided a while ago.
Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
You know what our school's like.
Everyone has unique circumstances.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh?
Your uniform made it in time, I see.
Yeah, it's a perfect fit.
Though it's slightly
different from Fushiguro's.
It has a hood, for one.
That's because the uniforms can
be customized upon request.
Huh?
But I never put in any requests.
I was the one who put in the custom order.
Whatever, I guess.
Be careful. Gojou-sensei has a
tendency to do things like that.
More importantly, why are
we meeting up in Harajuku?
Because it's what she asked for.
Hey, popcorn! I want some!
Oh, hello there. Are you
on the clock right now?
No, I'm not.
You see, I'm looking for potential models.
This is who I am.
Would you be interested?
I'm in a hurry right now.
Just hear me out!
Hey, you.
What about me?
Her?!
For the modeling gig, duh.
I'm asking what you think about me.
Oh, um, I'm in a hurry at the moment...
What the hell?
Don't run from me! Come out and say it!
We're about to go talk to her?
I'm sorry! Please let me go!
This is kinda embarrassing.
So are you.
Hey!
Over here!
Damn, what's up with that blindfold?
400 Yen Corner
Okay, once again.
Kugisaki Nobara.
Be happy, boys.
I'm the one woman in your group.
Stare...
Episode 3: Girl of Steel
I'm Itadori Yuuji. I'm from Sendai.
Fushiguro Megumi.
Kugisaki's POV
He looks like a potato.
He's definitely the type that
ate his own boogers as a kid.
And only a name here?
I can't stand high-and-mighty dudes.
I bet he likes setting
oil-slicked gulls on fire.
I always get stuck with
unfortunate circumstances.
She took one look and sighed.
Are we going somewhere from here?
We do have all three of you together.
Not to mention, two of you
are from the countryside.
So of course we're going
on a tour of Tokyo!
Tokyo
Tokyo! Tokyo! Tokyo!
We love Tokyo!
Huh?
TDL! I want to go to TDL!
Idiot! TDL's in Chiba!
Let's go to Chinatown, Sensei!
Chinatown's in Yokohama!
Yokohama's part of Tokyo!
Don't you know that? Look at a map!
The hell?! Quit spouting nonsense!
I will now announce our destination.
Roppongi
Roppongi!
Roppongi?!
There's a curse here.
You liar!
This isn't even Roppongi!
You were toying with us country folk!
There's a big cemetery nearby.
The double whammy of that and an
abandoned building brought out a curse.
Who does he think is responsible
for the rice he gets to eat, huh?!
So they really do pop up
more often around graves?
The issue isn't the cemetery itself.
It's the fact that people
associate cemeteries with fear.
Oh, it was the same
for schools, too, wasn't it?
Hold up. He didn't even know that yet?
To be honest...
He swallowed a special-grade cursed object?!
Gross! Unbelievable!
That's so unsanitary and disgusting!
No way, no way, no way, no way!
What?!
I agree with her.
I want to know what all of you are capable of.
Just think of this as a field test.
Nobara, Yuuji,
you two go exorcise the
curse inside that building.
Geh.
Huh? But I thought only curses
could exorcise curses, right?
I can't use any jujutsu yet.
You're basically half a curse already.
There's cursed energy
flowing throughout your body.
Though controlling that energy isn't
something you can learn overnight,
so use this.
It's the cursed tool, Slaughter Demon.
It's a weapon imbued with cursed energy.
It'll work on curses, too.
Lame.
Oh, one more thing.
Don't let Sukuna out.
If you use him, you'll get rid
of all the curses nearby in a flash,
but you'll also drag everyone around into it.
Got it. I won't let Sukuna out.
Hurry it up.
Yeah, yeah.
Go on, now!
I think I'll go, too.
Don't push yourself. You're still recovering.
But someone needs to keep
an eye on Itadori, right?
True.
But the one we're testing
this time is Nobara.
What a pain.
Why do I have to deal with curses
after coming all the way to Tokyo?
Huh? Didn't you come here to exorcise curses?
Let's save some time and split up.
I'll start from the top and go floor by floor.
You start from the bottom.
Let's get this over with quick
and grab some sushi from Ginza.
Hold on a minute.
Let's take this a bit more seriously.
Curses are dangerous, you know.
I don't wanna hear it from someone
who was a normie until recently!
Now get moving!
Your emotions have been
all over the place today!
This is why girls don't like you!
How did you know they don't like me?!
Are you even popular enough to talk? Bitch.
Do... you need... a receipt?
It's a curse!
Yeah, I can really move!
That Yuuji...
He's missing a few up here.
He has no hesitation
when it comes to killing these things
that take the form of living creatures,
albeit bizarre-looking ones, to try to kill him.
And it's not like he's been familiar
with curses for a long time, like you.
This is a boy who used to
live a normal high school life.
You've seen plenty of jujutsu sorcerers,
even those with talent,
give up in frustration because
they couldn't conquer
their fear or disgust, haven't you?
So today I want to confirm how crazy she is.
Hey, you, curse.
I mean you, mannequin in the center.
You actually think you're hidden there?
If you won't come out,
I'll just exorcise you there.
But Kugisaki has experience, right?
Little late for that now, isn't it?
Curses are born from human minds.
So their strength and numbers grow
in proportion to the population.
Do you think Nobara understands...
that curses in Tokyo are on a different
level than those in the countryside?
Kugisaki
Curses are born from human minds.
Broken Van
Filth
Serves you right
Go back to Tokyo
Leave
So their strength and numbers grow
in proportion to the population.
Curses in Tokyo are on a different
level than those in the countryside.
You might want to pull those out...
or my cursed energy will flow into you.
Nailed it.
A child?
Must have snuck in for some fun
and encountered the curse.
Hey, it's all right now. Come on out.
Huh?!
I guess it's true that kids don't
warm up to beautiful women.
Guess I'll call Itadori.
Wait!
Don't leave me here!
It's taking him hostage?
This curse has intelligence?!
When I say "level," I don't just mean
the amount of cursed energy they have.
It's their cunning.
Monsters that have gained wisdom will
often force cruel choices upon you...
with the weight of human lives in the balance.
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Damn it!
This curse isn't even all that strong!
Grade 4...
Maybe even lower, like a low grade 3!
But it's aware of that!
That's why it chose to take a hostage!
Calm yourself down.
If I die, the child dies, too.
But if the child dies, I won't die.
Logically speaking,
it's better if I survive, at least!
I'm unarmed.
Let the boy go.
I'm such an idiot!
See? It's not letting him go at all!
I wish I could have seen
Saori-chan one last time.
Huh? I missed?
You okay?
Uh-huh.
It's getting away!
I don't think so!
Itadori!
Give me that arm!
Huh?
I'll exorcise it.
Hold on.
A straw doll?
Creepy.
Straw Doll Technique:
Resonance!
Nice.
She's crazy, all right.
We won.
This bridge is dangerous
due to deterioration from age
and can no longer be used.
When I was in first grade,
Saori-chan moved to our village from Tokyo.
She was as cute as a doll,
and as kind as a nun.
Sticker Book
Yet Saori-chan was
ostracized by the villagers.
"She thinks country folk are dumb," they said,
letting themselves get paranoid,
We Protest the Kitagawa Highway Extension!
and in the end...
they drove her out.
Home for Sale
Broken Van
Filth
Serves you right
Go back to Tokyo
Leave
Calling it sickening wouldn't be enough.
She brought all these homemade
sweets I'd never heard of and said,
"The ones from the bakery are even better,"
with a smile as she treated me to them.
This bridge is dangerous
due to deterioration from age
and can no longer be used.
If I had stayed in that village...
This is why I told you
it's dangerous to go alone and
you need to take it seriously!
You never said it was dangerous to go alone!
I... didn't?!
And what have you been eating that lets you
punch through a wall with your bare hand?!
It wasn't reinforced concrete!
Even if it was, that'd still be
impossible for most people!
Most people?
You know, you've asked me
plenty of questions already,
but why did you come to Jujutsu Tech?
Why?
Because I hate the countryside,
and I wanted to live in Tokyo!
This was the only way I could move to the city
without having to worry about money!
You can risk your life over that?
I can.
After all, it means being true to myself.
If I had stayed in that village,
I'd be as good as dead.
Saori-chan, I made it to Tokyo.
If we ever meet here,
take me to that bakery you mentioned.
So as far as that goes, I'm grateful to you, too.
There wouldn't have been
a bright future if I had died or
I had been the only one to survive.
Thanks.
Well, having a more serious reason
doesn't make anyone better than the rest.
Okay, I've given you my
thanks, so that's all over!
We're even now!
What's wrong with her?
I live over there! Thanks again!
Did you know I get into a
foul mood when I'm hungry?
When are you not in a foul mood?
Good Joseph!
We made sure the kid got home.
Now shall we go grab some food?
Steak!
Sushi!
Leave it all to me!
And you, Megumi?
Okay, let's go.
Oh, I forgot about my
biggest haul of the day.
Hey, you, go fetch my things.
Harajuku
Coin Locker
Huh? Why should I do it?
I thought we were even.
We won thanks to my cursed energy.
Got a problem with that?
What about my raw strength?
Your monstrous power
from eating weird shit?
It's not just that!
Right, Fushiguro?
Huh? What's the matter, Fushiguro?
Nothing.
He's pouting because he
didn't get to join in.
What a child.
Log: July 2018
Log: July 2018.
West Tokyo City
Eishuu Juvenile Detention Center
West Tokyo City,
Eishuu Juvenile Detention Center.
In the sky above the exercise yard
In the sky above the exercise yard.
Hey...
What's that?
What?
Unnamed Apparition of Potential Special Grade
Unnamed Apparition
of Potential Special Grade.
Its curse womb was witnessed by several non-jujutsu sorcerers.
Its curse womb was witnessed
by several non-jujutsu sorcerers.
That up there! Looks like an egg.
What are you talking about?
Due to the emergency nature,
three Jujutsu Tech first-years were dispatched to the scene,
three Jujutsu Tech first-years
were dispatched to the scene,
and one died.
Juju Stroll
Itadori. I'm going with paper.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, yeah!
Sushi, huh? Guess we can go
to the usual place in Ginza.
Ginza, yahoo!
I want revolving sushi!
Ugh! Itadori, you're such a...
Ugh! Fushiguro, say something to him!
I'd rather get something
that tastes good if we're going.
Gojou-sensei's paying, anyway.
Revolving sushi is its own thing,
just like how yakisoba and instant
yakisoba are different things!
And I want to eat sushi.
Sushi's just a meal, but
revolving sushi's a leisure activity!
Like a theme park! Or TDL!
Also, Kugisaki, you said you
were from the country too,
so have you ever been to
a revolving sushi place?!
My favorite is Sushi Go,
but I'd go with Splendid Sushi
for someone's first time.
You get it, Sensei!
Hey, no one's said we're going yet.
Kugisaki, listen closely.
At Splendid Sushi...
the sushi comes to you on a bullet train.
Wha?!
Driver, this girl's never
had revolving sushi before.
*Please ride in cars properly and safely.
Take us to the Splendid Sushi with the
huge-ass parking lot along the interstate!
Episode 4:
Curse Womb Must Die
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org